Peyton Rous Papers 1909-1970 Mss.B.R77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1917-1970; 47.0 Linear feet (Box 1-85)
  - Publication Department - Rockefeller Institute, Journal of Experimental Medicine, 42 folders
    - Jungeblut, Claus W (Folder 32)
    - LeGros Clark, W E (Folder 32)
    - Livingston, E. & S., Ltd. (Folder 32)
    - Parker, James (Folder 32)
    - Whipple, G H (Folder 32)
    - Macy, Josiah, Jr., Foundation (Folder 32)
    - Mayer, Manfred M (Folder 32)
    - Menkin, Valy (Folder 32)
    - Morton, Harry E (Folder 32)
    - Mote, John R (Folder 32)
    - Ovary, Zoltan (Folder 32)
    - Pappenheimer, A M (Folder 32)
    - Pelloja, Mario (Folder 32)
    - Pitzman, Marsh (Folder 33)
    - Pullinger, B D (Folder 33)
    - Race, R R (Folder 33)
    - Raska, Sigwin B (Folder 33)
    - Rosner, Samuel (Folder 33)
    - Atlas, Mrs. Walter (Folder 33)
    - Crutcher, K G (Folder 33)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 33)
    - Sanyal, S N (Folder 33)
    - Sherman, James M (Folder 33)
    - Edsall, Geoffrey (Folder 33)
    - Smith, Margaret H.D. (Folder 34)
    - Snell, P Edson (Folder 34)
    - Snyder, John C (Folder 34)
    - Staple, P H (Folder 34)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 34)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 34)
    - Taylor, R M (Folder 34)
    - Trasino, Mario (Folder 34)
    - Trent, Mrs. Josiah C (Folder 34)
    - Year Book Publishers (Folder 34)
    - Friedewald, William F (Folder 34)
    - Waverly Press, Inc. (Folder 34)
    - Whipple, George H (Folder 34)
    - Wiener, Alexander S (Folder 34)
    - Wolf, A V (Folder 34)
    - Wood, W Barry, Jr. (Folder 34)
    - American College of Physicians (Folder 35)
    - Loveland, E R (Folder 35)
    - Bader, W J (Folder 35)
    - Branham, V C (Folder 35)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 35)
    - Pappenheimer, A M (Folder 35)
    - Dick, George F (Folder 35)
    - Avery, O T (Folder 35)
    - Ewens, Arthur E (Folder 35)
    - Farrar & Rinehart (Folder 36)
    - Fasciolo, J C (Folder 36)
    - Gasser, Herbert S (Folder 36)
    - Geschickter, Charles F (Folder 36)
    - Goodman, Louis S (Folder 36)
    - Goodpasture, Ernest W (Folder 36)
    - Briggs, Edith (Folder 36)
    - Heggie, Robert (Folder 36)
    - Jordan, H E (Folder 36)
    - Lancet (Folder 36)
    - Morland, Egbert (Folder 36)
    - Mudd, Stuart (Folder 36)
    - Madden, Sidney C (Folder 36)
    - Thalhimer, William (Folder 36)
    - Whipple, George (Folder 36)
    - Swift, Homer F (Folder 36)
    - Gudakunst, Don W (Folder 37)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis (Folder 37)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 37)
    - New England, Journal of Medicine (Folder 37)
    - Davies, Clara D (Folder 37)
    - Pappenheimer, A M, Jr. (Folder 37)
    - Schroeder, Henry A (Folder 37)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 37)
    - Strong, R P (Folder 37)
    - U.S. Surgeon General (Folder 37)
    - Tompkins, Edna H (Folder 37)
    - Vakil, Rustom Jal (Folder 37)
    - Rivers, Thomas M (Folder 37)
    - Williams, W H (Folder 37)
    - Winslow, C.E. A (Folder 37)
    - Wright, H. D. (Folder 37)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, Inc. (Folder 38)
    - Severinghaus, Aura E (Folder 38)
    - Arlington Chemical Co. (Folder 38)
    - Stowell, Leland E (Folder 38)
    - Babkin, B P (Folder 38)
    - Bergman, Lester V (Folder 38)
    - Boyd, William C (Folder 38)
    - Broadbent, Margaret (Folder 38)
    - Butler, Allan M (Folder 38)
    - Culosi, Jennie (Folder 38)
    - De Esbjorn, G J (Folder 38)
    - Ross, Lee (Folder 38)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 38)
    - Dunham, George C (Folder 38)
    - Dutchess, Charles E (Folder 39)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P (Folder 39)
    - Evans, Marie A (Folder 39)
    - Flinn, Waldo R (Folder 39)
    - Fowler, Virginia M (Folder 39)
    - Fowler, W M (Folder 39)
    - Gotthoffer, N R (Folder 39)
    - Hagan, William A (Folder 39)
    - Haurowitz, Felix (Folder 39)
    - Heidelberger, Michael (Folder 39)
    - Hazeltine, Mrs. Norma (Folder 39)
    - Reinman, Hobart (Folder 40)
    - Hoopes, Edna M (Folder 40)
    - Peters, Charlotte H (Folder 40)
    - Journal of Neurophysiology (Folder 40)
    - Keller, Alvin E (Folder 40)
    - Koteen, Herbert (Folder 40)
    - McClellan, H H (Folder 40)
    - Miller, C Philip (Folder 40)
    - Miller, Elizabeth (Folder 40)
    - National Research Council (Folder 40)
    - New York Academy of Medicine (Folder 40)
    - Puffer, Ruth R (Folder 40)
    - Slater, F (Folder 40)
    - Winter General Hospital (Folder 40)
    - Spivack, Lawrence E (Folder 40)
    - Gould, Zelda (Folder 40)
    - Squibb, E.R., & Sons (Folder 40)
    - Church, C. F. (Folder 40)
    - Steele, Murray (Folder 41)
    - Freygang, Dorothea (Folder 41)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P (Folder 42)
    - Taft, A E (Folder 42)
    - Wesson, Miley B (Folder 42)
    - Wetzel, Norman C (Folder 42)
    - Wiener, Maria (Folder 42)
    - Wright, A W (Folder 42)
  - Publishers
  - Puck, Theodore T
  - Pullinger, B D
    - Johansson, K R
    - Walter, William A
  - Punch
  - Purdy, W J
  - Purves, Austin
  - Putnam, Windsor B
  - Quarfoth, H J
  - Queen, Frank B
    - Horn, Robert C., Jr.
  - Quinn, Mrs. Clotilde Frilley
  - Rabinovitch, P
  - Rachmilewitz, M
    - Rosin, Anna
  - Rackemann, Francis M
  - Radar, Nancy Lurah
    - Scarborough, J Elliott
  - Rake, Geoffrey W
  - Rall, David P
  - Randolph, J W
  - Rappaport, Ben Z
  - Rapaport, Mauricio
  - Rappleye, Willard C
  - Rappoport, Arthur Everett
  - Ratcliffe, Herbert L
  - Ratner, Bret
  - Ratner, S
  - Ravdin, Isidore S
  - Rawson, Rulon W
  - Ray, O M
  - Read, A C
  - Read, Mrs. Dallas
  - Read, Isaac W
  - Read, Mrs. Mary
  - Read, Mrs. Nicholas Cabell
    - Johnson, Mrs. Dallas
    - Clark, R Lee, Jr.
    - Heinz, Erich
  - Read, R R
  - Reader's Digest
  - Ready, Mrs. Jack E
  - Recommendations and Introductions
  - Reddy, D Jaganatha
  - Redish, Milton H
  - Reed, Thomas B
  - Rees, David T
  - Rehbock, Donald J
  - Reid, Helen (Mrs. Ogden Reid)
  - Reid, Lynne
  - Reid, Roger D
  - Reif, Arnold E
  - Reimann, Stanley P
  - Reiner-Deutsch, W
  - Reinhard, Melvin C
  - Reis, Alfred J
  - Reprints: (Requests for, and Thank You Letters)
  - Research Corporation
    - Schauer, Charles H
  - Reticulo-Endothelial System Society.
    - Heller, John H
  - Reynals, Francisco Duran-
    - Bayne-Jones, S
  - Reyniers, James A
  - Reynolds, Frederick P
  - Reys, Mary
    - Marchini, Anthony
  - Reznikoff, Paul
  - Rhea, Lawrence J
  - Rhoads, Cornelius P
  - Rice, Fannie Y
  - Rice, George D
  - Rice, John H
  - Rich, Arnold R
  - Richards, Alfred N
  - Richards, Bernard G
  - Richards, Dickinson W
  - Richardson, Edward H
  - Richardson, Henry B
  - Richet, Charles
  - Richmond, Mrs. Charles A
  - Rideal, Eric K
    - Duggan, Stephen P
    - Flinn, Waldo R
    - Carrel, Alexis
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Landsteiner, Karl
  - Riegal, Byron
  - Riegel, Ilse L
  - Rienhoff, William F
  - Riesman, David
  - Rigdon, R H
  - Rile, Mrs. E S S
  - Riley, Vernon
  - Risley, D E
  - Riveros, M
    - Dean, H. R.
    - Moe, Henry Allen
    - Pack, George T
  - Rivers, Thomas M
  - Robbilard, Basil
  - Robbins, Frank E
  - Robbins, William Jacob
  - Roberts, Henry
  - Roberts, S C
  - Robertson, A D
  - Robertson, L Bruce
  - Robertson, O H
    - Bell, Whitfield Jenks, Jr.
    - Robertson, Mrs. Ruth
    - Corner, George W
    - Puck, Theodore T
    - Coggeshall, Lowell T
    - Long, Esmond R
    - Mollison, P L
  - Robey, William H
  - Robinson, G Canby
  - Robinson, Meyer H
  - Robison, Mrs. Elizabeth
  - Rockefeller, David
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
  - The Rockefeller Foundation
    - Oliver, Wade W
  - Rockefeller Institute
    - Bronk, Detlev W
    - Rous, Simonne
    - Flinn, Waldo R
    - Petrzelka, Charles
  - Rockefeller Institute. Board of Scientific Directors
  - Rockefeller Institute - Business Manager
  - Rockefeller Institute. Reports for Boards of Directors.
    - Bronk, Detlev W
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Rivers, Thomas M
    - Biemiller, Reynard
  - Rockefeller Institute Press
    - Campbell, Charles I
  - Rockefeller Institute Quarterly
    - Campbell, Charles I
  - Rockefeller University
    - Lucius, Marian E
    - Elliot, Roger C
    - McCarty, Maclyn
    - Seitz, Frederick
    - Bayless, William A
  - Roe, Francis J C
  - Roeder, Adolph
  - Rogers, Charles C
  - Rogers, Mrs. Charles C
  - Roger, Mrs. Clifton
  - Rogers, E Stanfield
    - Beard, Joseph W
    - Waters, L L
    - Sprunt, Douglas H
    - Wuest, Margaret
    - Barry, Guy T
    - Bennett, H Stanley
    - Bond, V P
  - Rogers, Florela
  - Rogers, Frances Colby
  - Rogers, John
  - Rogers, Mrs. John Jacob
  - Rolleston, H D
  - Romanzi, Carmine A
  - Romeyn, J A
  - Rondoni, Pietro
  - Roof, Betty Sams
    - Goldforb, A J
    - Willett, Forrest M
    - Smith, Lloyd H
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Eleanor
  - Rosbash, David
  - Rose, Wicliffe
    - Cole, Rufus
    - Fricks, L D
  - Rose, William Brandt
  - Rose, William C
  - Rosenau, M J
  - Rosenberg, L Charles
  - Rosenberg, Esther
  - Rosengarten, A G., Jr.
  - Rosenow, E C
  - Rosenthal, S M
  - Rosin, Anne
  - Roskin, Gr
  - Rothschild, Victor
  - Rous, Cestmir
  - Rous, Charles
    - Scott, Walter
  - Rous, Mrs. Fannie
  - Rous, Peyton
    - The Activating, Transforming, and Carcinogenic Effects of the Rabbit Papilloma Virus (Shope) Upon Implanted Tar Tumors [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - Ad Virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Anomalous Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Anomalone, Rous, Peyton
    - Are Carcinogens Responsible for the Superimposed Neoplastic Changes... Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Autobiographical Sketch, Rous, Peyton
    - Autobiographical Sketch (Notes), Rous, Peyton
    - Best Tar Paper (Photographs), Rous, Peyton
    - Bibliography, Rous, Peyton
    - CA Prep, Rous, Peyton
    - The CA Problem Viewed Today, Rous, Peyton
    - The Cancer Problem Now: A Roving Commentary, Rous, Peyton
    - Cancers deriving from the Virus Papillomas of Wild Rabbits under natural Conditions [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - Carcinogenesis with A virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Cell Vxs. Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - The Challenge to Man of the Neoplastic Cell [Nobel Prize Lecture], Rous, Peyton
    - Character of Tar and MC Tumors, Rous, Peyton
    - Chicken Tumors, Rous, Peyton
    - Comb Tumors, Domestic Rabbit, Rous, Peyton
    - A Comparison of Virus-Induced Rabbit Tumors with the Tumors of Unknown Cause Elicited by Tarring [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - "Composite" Paper and Betty Roof's Tables, Rous, Peyton
    - Concerning Blood Banks, Rous, Peyton
    - Concerning Carcinogenesis, Rous, Peyton
    - Concerning Reticulo-Endothelial Cells [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Beard, J. W.
    - Conditional Neoplasms and Sub-Threshhold Neoplastic States... [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - Conditional Reappearing Tar Tumors and their Significance [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - The Conditions Determining Cancer, Rous, Peyton
    - Correspondence Listing... Secretarial Notes, Rous, Peyton
    - Dance of Death (Stuff Omitted), Rous, Peyton
    - Deeply Hidden Neoplastic Potentialities of Tarred Rabbit Epidermis, Rous, Peyton
    - Deeply Latent Neoplastic Cells, Rous, Peyton
    - Detergents, Rous, Peyton
    - Detroit Lecture, Rous, Peyton
    - The Disagreement Amongs Lectures, Rous, Peyton
    - Discing, Rous, Peyton
    - Discing Early. Domestic Rabbit 3053, Rous, Peyton
    - Dissociation of Pap Virus and Antibodies, Rous, Peyton
    - Do Mouse Tumor Cells Respond to a Carcinogen by Changing Further? [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Dumbell, Keith
    - Domestic Rabbit 3054 - Photos, Rous, Peyton
    - Domestic Rabbit 3045 - Photos, Rous, Peyton
    - Domestic Rabbit 3065, 2098, 3050, 3044 Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Dualism, Rous, Peyton
    - Dyes - Technical About Gradient, Rous, Peyton
    - Early Action on Retiring Allowance (Personal), Rous, Peyton
    - Effect of the Tumor Viruses upon thought on Cancer Causation, Rous, Peyton
    - Emergency Distribution of the Blood Service, Rous, Peyton
    - The Experimental Disclosure of Latent Neoplastic Changes in Tarred Skin [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and MacKenzie, Ian
    - Experiments on the Cause of Some Cancers, Rous, Peyton
    - Experiments on the Cause of Tumors, Rous, Peyton
    - Facts and Thoughts called forth by a gravel pit that may aid some Housatonic folk, Rous, Peyton
    - Fasting, Rous, Peyton
    - The Final Vascular Responses, Rous, Peyton
    - First Chicken Ts. Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Forloewi Resume, Rous, Peyton
    - For Pennsylvania, 1948; Rous, Peyton
    - Frill Horns, Rous, Peyton
    - Further work on the Carcinogenetic Activities of a virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Future Lecture (?), Rous, Peyton
    - Gates' Autobiography, Rous, Peyton
    - General Lecture, Dec. 7, 1950; Rous, Peyton
    - Gravel Banks.., Rous, Peyton
    - Comb Tumors: Deeply Latent Neoplastic Cells, Rous, Peyton, Grey et al.
    - Description of Plates, Rous, Peyton and Grey
    - Harvey Lecture, Rous, Peyton
    - Henderson's Personal Work to be done with me, Rous, Peyton
    - History of Virus Discovery, Etc, Rous, Peyton
    - Hormones, Rous, Peyton
    - Host Resistance Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - House, Rous, Peyton
    - Hydrolysis of Pap Tissues, Rous, Peyton
    - Inaugural Lecture - Caspari Hall, Rous, Peyton
    - Infection of the Ectoderm... Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - An Inflicted Gravel Pit, Rous, Peyton
    - Influence of Hereditary Malformations on Carcinogenesis in "Crew" Mice.., Rous, Peyton
    - An Inquiry into the effect of old custom upon the behavior of town zoning Boards Nowadays, Rous, Peyton
    - Joint Action of a Carcinogenic virus and a chemical carcinogen to Induce Cancer [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Rogers, Stansfield
    - The Known causes of cancer, Rous, Peyton
    - Lab, Assistants, Secretaries, etc, Rous, Peyton
    - Laboratory Report, Rous, Peyton and Henderson, James S.
    - Lantern Talk in Baltimore, 1911; Rous, Peyton
    - Latency, Rous, Peyton
    - Latent. Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - The Least Neoplastic Deviations from the Normal in Tarred Rabbit Skin, Rous, Peyton
    - Lecture Notes, Rous, Peyton
    - Lentigos, Rous, Peyton
    - Leukemia SV40 and Adeno-Vs Chromosomes, Rous, Peyton
    - List of Chemicals, Rous, Peyton
    - Lung Tumors for Paps (Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - Masking, Rous, Peyton
    - MC Embryo, Rous, Peyton
    - Microbiological and Cancer Congress Paper, 1939; Rous, Peyton
    - Milk Virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Minimal Neoplastic Changes in Tarred Rabbit Skins, Rous, Peyton
    - Miscellaneous Notes, Rous, Peyton
    - Miscellaneous Notes for Talks, Rous, Peyton
    - Miscellaneous Notes on Cancer and Viruses, Rous, Peyton
    - Miscellaneous Notes on Cancer and Viruses, Rous, Peyton
    - Morphological Evidence of Virus Presence, Rous, Peyton
    - Nature - Don't Use!, Rous, Peyton
    - Nature - Dubious, Rous, Peyton
    - Neoplastic Yield of Repeated Rediscings of Tarred Ears, Rous, Peyton
    - Notes for a Lecture, Rous, Peyton
    - Notes for a new Lecture, Rous, Peyton
    - Nude Pap, Rous, Peyton
    - The Occurrence in Tarred Rabbit skin of Minor... Neoplastic Changes [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Rogers, Stansfield
    - The Occurrence of Well-Nigh Imperceptible Neoplastic Deviations from the Normal in Tarred Skin, Rous, Peyton
    - Occurrence of Unique Deeply Subthreshold Neoplastic Changes in Rabbit Epidermis Tarred Long Before, Rous, Peyton
    - On Virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Osteochondrosarcomas - Human and Chicken, Rous, Peyton
    - Outcome of the Repeated Discing of Normal Ears, Rous, Peyton
    - Pap MC - Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Papilloma. Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Pathological Consequences of the Gradient, Rous, Peyton
    - Pathology and the Glare of the Future, Rous, Peyton
      Weller, Carl V
    - Personal, Rous, Peyton
      - McMasters
      - Flexner, Simon
      - Burlingham, Charles C
      - Stone, William S
      - Watts, Mrs. Philip B
      - Schloss, Mrs. Rowena
      - Ewing, James
      - Fowler, Persis Billington
      - Passport
      - American Express
      - Banks
      - Firms, Etc
      - DeKay, Mrs. Charles
      - New York Telephone Company
      - Stephenson, Carl
      - Read
      - Blalock, Alfred
      - Muller, Paul
      - Catesby Jones, T
      - Dochez, A Raymond
      - Darling, C Douglas
      - Chase, Jessie
      - Schorer, Mark
      - Wilson, Thomas J
      - Oberling, Charles
      - Baldwin, Horace
      - Bronk, Detlev W
      - Corscaden, James Albert
      - Hoffnagle, James H.
      - Haddow, A.
      - Haagensen, C. D.
    - Personal- Real Estate, Rous, Peyton
    - Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Physical Examination, Rous, Peyton
    - Physiological Factors in the Genesis of Gall-Stones, Rous, Peyton
    - Physiological Pathology of Obstructed Bile Passages, Rous, Peyton
    - Plan of Tests for Masked Virus, Rous, Peyton; Kidd, John G.; and Friedewald, William F.
    - Plates for Surmise and Fact, Rous, Peyton
    - Plating of Tumor Components. (Photographs), Rous, Peyton
    - Plating out of Tumor Components in the Subcutaneous expanses of Young Mice, Rous, Peyton
    - Polyoma, Rous, Peyton
    - Possible Relation of Hair Intrusion to Comb Tumors, Rous, Peyton
    - Potentiality, Rous, Peyton
    - Present knowledge concerning viruses as a cause of Tumors, 1936; Rous, Peyton
    - Presence of Deeply Latent neoplastic cells in Rabbit epidermis tarred long before, Rous, Peyton
    - Present knowledge concerning Viruses as a cause of tumors [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - Present knowledge of Carcinogenesis, Rous, Peyton
    - Present knowledge concerning viruses as a cause of tumors, Rous, Peyton
    - Presentation of the Gold Headed cane, Rous, Peyton
    - Progression Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - The Progression to Ca, Rous, Peyton
    - Quanah, Texas, Rous, Peyton
    - Rockefeller Institute Budget, Rous, Peyton
      - Bronk, Detlev W.
    - The relation of a Rabbit Papilloma virus (Shope) to Cancer Causation [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - Relation of Filterable Agents to Tumor Formation [Abstract], Rous, Peyton
    - The Relation of Viruses and Tumors [Abstract], Rous, Peyton
    - Remarks Presenting Dr. Huggins for the Charles L. Mayer Award, Rous, Peyton
    - Reports to Rockefeller Institute, Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1909-1915; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1911 May; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1912 Jan.; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1912 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1912 June; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1912-13; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1913 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1913 June; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1913-14.; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1914 January: April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1914 May; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1915 January; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1915 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1915 June; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1915-16; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1916 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1916 June; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1916-17; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1917 January; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1917 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1918 January; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1918 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1918 October; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1918-19; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1919 June; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1919 October; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1920 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1921 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1921 September; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1922 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1922 October; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1923 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1923 October; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, (1923?); Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1924 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1924; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1925 September; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1926 Spring; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1926 Fall; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1927 Spring; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1927 Spring; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, March 24, 1928; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1929 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report:, 1930 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1931 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1932 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1933 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1934 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1935 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1936 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1939 Spring; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1940; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1941; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1942 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1943 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1944 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1945 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1946; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1947 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1948 April; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1949; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1950 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1954 March; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1954 May; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1957-8; Rous, Peyton
      - Report, 1958-9(?); Rous, Peyton
      - Report Requested by Gasser, September 28, 1939; Rous, Peyton
    - Rous Sarcoma and Rous Sarcoma Virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Salivary Gland Virus and Cancer, Rous, Peyton
    - Sarcoma Steps Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - The Scope of Carcinogensis, Rous, Peyton
    - Search for the Activating Cause of the Cancers Arising from the Virus-Induced Rabbit Papillomas, Rous, Peyton and Rogers, Stansfield
    - Sequential Neoplastic Changes. (Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - The Share in the Production of a fowl Sarcoma of a Filterable agent, Rous, Peyton
      - Flexner, Simon
      - Murphy, James B
    - Shope Virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Simon Flexner, Rous, Peyton
    - The Social Ointment's own fly, Rous, Peyton
    - Steeping. Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Stim Tar, Rous, Peyton
    - Stim Tar Paper (Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - Stim Tar Talks, Rous, Peyton
    - Structural Drawings, Rous, Peyton
    - Summation. Photographs, Rous, Peyton
    - Swamp Hare (Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - "Surmise and Fact", Rous, Peyton
      - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
      - Huxley, Sir Julian
      - Larin, Nicholas M
      - Laurence, William L
      - Medawar, Peter B
      - Reed, T Edward
      - Stanton, Mearl F
      - Tannenbaum, Albert
      - Tanner, Howard A
      - Wohl, Sonia S
      - Wrinch, Dorothy
    - Symposium on Cancer, Rous, Peyton
    - Talk to Board of Directors, Rockefeller Institute, January 17, 1942; Rous, Peyton
    - Talk with Dubos, February 14, 1942; Rous, Peyton
    - Talk to the Board of Directors of Rockefeller Institute, 1942 Jan. 17; Rous, Peyton
    - Tar Cancers, Rous, Peyton
    - Tar Cancers in Mice, Rous, Peyton
    - Tar Tumor (Chicken #1) Photos, Rous, Peyton
    - Tar Tumors of White Rabbits, Rous, Peyton
    - Three Apparatuses for Culture, Rous, Peyton
    - Tissue Neglect During Emergencies of the Body, Rous, Peyton
    - A Transplantable Rabbit Carcinoma Originating in a Virus-Induced Papilloma... [Abstract], Rous, Peyton and Kidd, John G.
    - Tumor changes Associated with the presence of Nuclear Inclusions, Rous, Peyton
    - The Tumor Characteristics of a Rabbit Growth (Shope) Caused by a Filterable Virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Tumors induced by Punching a Normal Rabbit's Ears, Rous, Peyton
    - Tumor-Virus Problems, Rous, Peyton
    - Two Stage: Delayed Fibromatosis, Rous, Peyton
    - Union in Vitro of the Papilloma Virus and its Antibody, Rous, Peyton
    - Variants, Rous, Peyton
    - Vascular Permeability as Conditioned by Age and Species Smith, Frederick, Rous, Peyton
    - Vascular Permeability as Conditioned by Age and Species, Rous, Peyton
    - Virus Hypothesis, Rous, Peyton
    - Virus Demonstration, Rous, Peyton
    - Virus Relationships to Tumors, Rous, Peyton